所以你申请了你的电话还是回了电话
So you put in your application,
you got a call back, or
也许是招聘者通过 LinkedIn 或电子邮件或其他方式联系到您，或者
maybe a recruiter reached out to you
via LinkedIn or email or something, or
你在一个聚会上认识了一个人没关系
you met someone at a meetup,
it doesn't matter.
应用程序已完成。
The application is done.
太好了
It's good.
您可以与招聘经理或招聘人员进行初始电话联系。
You have the initial phone call with
the hiring manager or the recruiter.
那你现在做什么
So what do you do now?
再说一次你会做的但我们从没想过
Again, something you will do,
but we never think about and
这个部分其实是很重要的。
this part is actually kind of important.
你应该准备好回应蝙蝠的问题
Questions that you should be prepared
to answer right off the bat.
我保证不管公司是谁
I guarantee it doesn't
matter who the company is,
他们会问这些事如果是招聘经理还是招聘者
they're gonna ask these things,
if it's a hiring manager or recruiter.
你现在做什么
What do you do currently?
你应该知道你的头应该有一个
You should know that like,
top your head you should have a one or
两个句子的答案。
two sentence answer.
我是杰姆
Me, I'm Jem.
我是 Netflix的高级工程师
I'm senior engineer at Netflix.
我在一个 UI 核心团队中工作，我构建了一些东西。
I work on one of the UI core teams and
I build stuff.
好吧他们会说什么的
That's fine,
they'll say what sort of stuff?
我想，我这几天做了很多 Node ，但在 Netflix 之前的角色中，
I'll be like, I do a lot of Node these
days, but in previous roles in Netflix,
我使用 React 与节点后端一起构建了许多 AB 测试。
I built a lot of AB tests using
React with the Node back end.
那是我想知道的
That's they I wanna know.
他们和很多人交谈，把它放下来，让你把它钉在下面。
They talk to a lot of people and
have it down, have you spiel down.
如果你已经在 7 个或 7 个
If you've ever done a recruiting
circuit where you've talked to seven or
八个公司当你找新工作的时候
eight companies at once,
when you look for a new job,
你知道这会是一次又一次又一次的出现
you know this will come up over and
over and over again, so just hone it now.
你要问的另一个问题是
Another question you are gonna get asked
is what are some of the projects you've
工作吗
worked on?
所以他们要找的是
So what they're looking for
你是在向后端或前端倾斜吗 ?
here is are you kind of leaning more
towards the backend or frontend?
节点，这类事情。
So Node, that sort of thing.
你是堆满堆的吗
Are you more full stack-y?
您是否重在辅助功能选项 ?
Are you heavy on accessibility?
你表现的重吗 ?
Are you heavy on performance?
你应该有你工作的项目，挑战是什么，
You should have the project you worked on,
what the challenges were, and
你是怎么克服他们的
how you overcame them.
这些问题都来了我向你保证
These questions will come up,
I promise you.
另一个是，你接下来要找的是什么 ?
Another one is, what are you looking for
in your next role?
我要更多的钱
I want more money.
这可能是真的你想多付一点钱
That's probably true,
you wanna get paid a little bit more, but
每个人都想多付一点钱
everybody wants to get
paid a little bit more.
你的下一个角色是什么
What are you looking for
in your next role?
所以说些什么，我不知道，也许你想学些什么。
So say something about, I don't know,
maybe you want to learn something.
你想和比你更聪明的人一起工作
You want to work with people
that are smarter than you,
我们都应该渴望的
which we should all aspire to.
你想和比你聪明的人合作所以我可以向他们学习
You wanna work with people who are smarter
than you, so I can learn from them.
或者我想解决有挑战性的项目
Or I wanna solve challenging projects.
或者我想给我的公司带来很大的影响
Or I wanna have a big
impact in my company.
我不想成为另一个在车轮里的懦夫
I don't wanna be another cog in the wheel,
things like that.
但你的下一个角色是什么
But have an idea of what you're
looking for in your next role,
他们会想知道的
cuz they're gonna wanna know.
你会让那些从第一次电话中被淘汰出来的人大吃一惊
And you'd be surprised the number people
that get vetted out from the first call.
我说，我是怎么做到的，我是说我们实际上不是这样做的，但是
I say, how did so and so
do I mean we don't actually do this, but
假设我的朋友是怎么做的
hypothetically, I'd be
like how did my friend do?
他们好像有点不像他们有个方向
They kind of mumbled a lot didn't
really seem like they had a direction.
他们真的不知道自己想做什么
They didn't really know what they want to
do and it's really hard to hire someone
不知道他们是否想为你工作
who doesn't know if they
even want to work for you.
给他们一个想雇你的理由
Give them a reason to want to hire you.
所以我真的很热情，真的很热情，但是我觉得我不能
So I'm really passionate, really
enthusiastic, but I don't think I can
以我现在的角色来学习，所以我想把它移到另一个项目上。
learn anymore in my current role, and so
I wanna move onto a different project.
或者我厌倦了我不知道财务空间
Or I'm tired of, I don't know,
the finance space, and
我想进入医疗服务之类的
I wanna move into healthcare,
something like that.
问题是，你为什么要为 x 工作 ?
The question really is,
why do you wanna work for x?
你为什么要为 Fronend Masters 工作
Why do you wanna work for
Frontend Masters?
有理由做些研究
Have a reason, do some research.
两分钟后到他们的网站看看他们的行动和理解
Take two minutes, go to their website,
look at what they do and understand
他们所拥有的项目，了解他们所面临的挑战。
the kind of projects they have, understand
the challenges they're working on.
最后一个是，接下来的步骤是什么 ?
And the last one is,
what is your availability for next steps?
因为那意味着他们喜欢你
Because that means they liked you.
这意味着他们想让你进入下一轮面试
That means that they wanna move you on
to the next round in the interview.
那你的可用性呢
So what's your availability?
您应该打开日历。
You should have your calendar open.
你说我每周五到四点都是免费的
You say like, hey,
every Friday at four o'clock I'm free.
所以我们可以进行电话屏蔽，密码测试，或者做什么。
So we can do a phone screening,
code test, or whatever.
但要做好准备
But be prepared.
我从来没有接到招聘者的电话
I've never not had a phone
call with a recruiter or
没有这些问题的招聘经理
hiring manager that didn't
have these questions on them.
我只想让你准备好
I just wanna get you ready.
如果你被要求思考一些问题，那就不是世界末日。
It's not the end of the world if
you're asked to think a little bit but
如果你能顺利的话就更容易了像个科学一样
it's a lot easier if you're just smooth,
got it down like a science.